They don't belong here.
White Settlers is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Simeon Halligan.
Young urban couple Ed and Sarah are set to begin a new life when they move
from London into an isolated borders Scottish farmhouse.
After falling in love with the 19th century Castle Farm and seeing its potential as
a fixer-upper they are anxious to get started on the renovations.
In bed on their first night Sarah thinks she can hear noises in the darkness but
Ed is disbelieving saying it’s her imagination playing tricks.
Persisting in her fear they are not alone in the
house, she forces Ed to investigate.
When he doesn’t return after a scarily long period, she goes downstairs to investigate
only to be confronted by a welcoming committee of masked intruders.
As she desperately searches for Ed, a terrifying game of cat
and mouse ensues with the mysterious assailants.
But what do they want and what horrors do they
have planned for the two newcomers?
Sarah, played by Pollyanna McIntosh.
Ed, played by Lee Williams.
Flo, played by Joanne Mitchell.
Local, played by James McCreadie.
Local, played by Dominic Kay.
White Settlers (also released as The Blood Lands) is a 2014 British
thriller-horror film that was directed by Simeon Halligan.
The film had its  premiere on 23 August 2014 at Film4 FrightFest and stars Pollyanna McIntosh and Lee
Williams as a couple that find that their new home is not as hospitable as they would have hoped.
The film explores themes of farm, mask, pig, scotland, knife.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.